pennyskateboards.com 2016-03-23

# Privacy Policy | Penny Skateboards Unites States

Absolute Board Co., Inc., a Delaware corporation ("Absolute"), believes in protecting your personal information and privacy. We take pride in the relationships we have been able to build with our customers and communities across the world. We believe our Privacy Policy reflects our commitment to our customers.

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83(c)(2), Absolute does not share its customers personal information with companies or others for the third parties' direct marketing use. 

* ### Information We Collect.

  * Information you provide when you request information from a site or purchase a product or service from us, including your address, telephone number, email address, and payment information.
  * Location information when you visit our sites, including information provided by a mobile device interacting with one of our sites, or location information associated with your IP address, where we are permitted by law to process this information. 
  * Usage, viewing, and technical data, including your IP address or device identifier, when you visit our sites, or open emails from us.

* ### Registration

We encourage you to register for an account with us when shopping on our websites; however, registration is not required. Our registration process requires customers to provide a name, a mailing address, a telephone number, cell phone, email address, and password. A user must verify he or she is 13 years of age or older in order to register. By registering with us, we can provide a better, simpler, and more interactive experience. The contact information you provide will be used to contact you regarding the status of your order, answer your questions, and, unless you choose to opt-out, to send you communications about upcoming sales, contests, promotions, product information, and similar notifications.

By registering you acknowledge and agree you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your registration information and password. You also acknowledge you are responsible for all of your use of the site under the registered account. 

* ### How We Collect Information.

We collect information you provide to us when you purchase products, request services, or other information from us, respond to customer surveys, register for an account with us or otherwise interact with us.

We automatically collect information through technology such as cookies, Flash cookies, log files, web beacons, and other technologies when you visit our sites or interact with or emails. A cookie is a small data file which our site leaves on your web browser, in order for the site to remember you and your personal preferences when you return to the site. 

* ### Cookies

You may adjust your browser settings to limit certain tracking features or to decline cookies; but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on our site or take full advantage of our offerings.

Customers can still utilize most of the features of our website without using cookies, including making a purchase, but we will not be able to recognize the customer as a returning user unless the customer logs in.

* ### How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals.

Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or similar mechanisms from some or all browsers. For detailed information on browser tracking signals, Do Not Track, and similar technologies, please visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.org/>.

* ### How We Use Your Information

Absolute or its agent will be the data manager for any information you provide. The relevant data manager can be determined here: 

Penny Skateboards uses YouTube and Vimeo to display campaign and content videos, please review YouTube ([www.youtube.com](http://www.youtube.com/)) and Vimeo's ([www.vimeo.com](http://www.vimeo.com/)) Privacy Polices as viewing our videos will subject you to their policies.

Basic personal information is sent to Global Collect (payment gateway) upon using http://www.pennyskateboards.com/us/ for the purchasing of goods.

Penny Skateboard also participates in a third party review and rating system to ensure you are provided unbiased, accurate and complete reviews to assist you in your purchasing. Details around the 'Customer Rating & Reviews' service is located at [clause 15.1 in our Terms and Conditions.](http://www.pennyskateboards.com/us/terms-conditions#review/)

Absolute or its agent may access your information, unless prohibited under applicable law, for the following purposes:

  * To provide you products and services; 
  * To analyze, optimize, and improve our products, and services; 
  * To communicate with you regarding your account, transactions, and information requests with Absolute; 
  * To provide you information regarding features on our sites or changes to our policies; and 
  * According to choices and controls that may be available to you: 
    * To send you emails, offers, and promotions for our products and services; and 
    * To personalize content and experiences on our sites. 

* ### How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or customer freight shipping. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to perform the service requested. Absolute takes reasonable steps to ensure these organizations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

* ### Your Controls and Choices.

We provide you certain controls and choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your information. In accordance with relevant law, your controls and choices may include:

  * Choices for email subscriptions, newsletters, alerts, and similar communications; 
  * Requests for access to the personal information we hold about you; and 
  * Requests for us or third parties to amend or delete personal information. 

* ### Children's Privacy.

We recognize the utmost importance of the need to protect the personal information of children. For this reason, we do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years old. Features on our sites which may collect personal information are age-gated so they are not available to children under 13 years old. If we do collect personal information from a child under 13 years old, we may maintain that information only as long as it is reasonably necessary as required by law, or to fulfill a request with parental consent. If we discover we possess information from a child under 13 in a manner inconsistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act's requirements, or other relevant laws, we will seek to delete the information immediately.

* ### Data Security, Integrity and Retention.

We are committed to the security, integrity, and confidentiality of your information. We have physical, administrative, electronic, and technical security measures which are designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized viewing, access, disclosure, use, and modification. We periodically review all security procedures to consider appropriate new measures which become available to us.

Despite all efforts, however, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We will retain your personal information for the length of time needed to fulfill any requests, and will strive to dispose of all personal information in a secure manner when the information is no longer reasonably necessary.

* ### Data Transfers, Storage and Processing Globally.

We operate globally and may transfer your personal information among Absolute, its parent company, or third parties in locations around the world for the purposes described in this privacy policy. Wherever and whenever your personal information is transferred, stored, or processed by us, we will strive to safeguard the privacy of your personal information.

* ### Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We may change this privacy policy to accommodate new technologies, adjust to new industry practices, or to abide by regulatory requirements. Changes are generally intended to provide greater protections of your personal information, or for other purposes. When we materially change this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you, where required by applicable law. Your continued use of the product or service, including use of any company website, after the effective date of the change will constitute acceptance of the change. We may provide such notice by email, by posting the notice on our sites, or by other means consistent with applicable law.

**Notice to California Residents:** If you are a California resident, you may have certain additional rights under California law. California Civil Code section 1798.83 allows you to request information regarding any disclosure of your personal information by Absolute to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or the privacy of your personal information, you can request more information or ask questions using the contact information provided below:

_This Privacy Policy was last updated September 15, 2015._
